ALEN BEGZIC

An Analytical User Experience Researcher and Designer with a background in project management. Offering a strong attention to detail and accuracy with exceptional critical thinking skills and problem solving. Committed to improving technological processes and

UX Design Research Projects

Fitness and Diet mobil application | Career Foundry Case Study Feb 2021 - Sept 2021

- Applied a user-centered design process and mobile first-approach to design a responsive
 application for users to personalize their own fitness journey with costume workout and diet plans
- Conducted competitive analysis, user interviews, surveys, A/B testing to gather valuable research data and develop personas, user flows and sitemaps.
- Designed 20+ high fidelity screens, mockups, prototypes and a style guide based on stakeholder requests.

Education

UX Design Immersion, CareerFoundry | Online | Nov 2020 - Oct 2021

500+ hours of UX Design/ UX Research study and implementation, resulting in the end-to-end design of applications. Specialized in UX Research.

Front End Development, Udacity | Online | Feb 2020 - Sep 2020

Intense project based learning program with a focus of front end development. Building web pages using HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

Experience

Project Manager, Complete Insulation and Fire Stopping | New York New York | **SEP 2020 - PRESENT**

- Worked as the point of contract for Clint through the project, asking and answering questions as needed
 - Oversee details regarding design evaluations
 - Process change orders and manage labor scheduling.

FreeLance UX Designer | Remote | January 2021 - Nov 2021

- Built client relationships pitching ideas towards Clints to help improve existing applications.
- Analyzed user behaviors and helped create user personas to help reach and discover target audiences.
 - Collaborating with other team members and coordinate details to reach our target outcome.



https://www.alenbegzic.com



www.linkedin.com/in/alenbegzic



abegzic1080@gmail.com



347-301-2749



https://alenbegzic.medium.com



New York, New York 11377

UX/UX-Research Design Skills

Designing and Implementing

Research Strategies

Exceptional behavioral data-

collecting analyzing skills.

User-Centered Design

Information Architecture

Wireframing

Prototyping

Web Design

Style Guides

Iconography

Personas

Usability Analysis

User Research

Storyboarding and Sitemaps

Card-Sorting

HTML, CSS and JavaScript

Tools

Figma

Sketch

InVision

Adobe XD

Balsamiq

Evolt

Lookback

Miro